making sure that everything is
synchronized and
absolutely running to time
not so very long ago Liverpool flash
bright in the FA Cup 6-1 at anfield
two of those six Liverpool goals were
bright and own goals it would be an
enormous surprise
if Liverpool were to sweep aside
Brighton so comfortably today on Sussex
turf
all right
is Tariq lamptey
very very talented
young man who has struggled to get
minutes in this fighting team this
season his throw-in is uh flicked on
the
tall goal as you touched on just a
moment ago Matt it's it's energy and
intensity is what Liverpool struggled to
find this season surprising isn't it
because it's the one thing that Jurgen
klopp brought to the club when he first
arrived seven years ago and they've
adapted brilliantly and obviously had
huge success along the way but I was at
this fixture in the Premier League with
Brighton we're absolutely superb in the
three-nil home win and Liverpool just
couldn't get anywhere near them they
dominated them with the ball with the
second uh ball possession you know
Energy across the park and I think this
is a chance for Liverpool to turn up in
a cup time and really put that right
foreign
goal today
who gave Trent Alexander a little bit of
a run around in that game yeah that was
a matchup that went well for Liverpool
at all in that game
John Alexander Arnold there looking a
little bit more determined in that
challenge there and told him a lovely
take and tried to get behind it but it's
under Arnold just matched him
it's going to need to deal with m1b1s
today because Brighton will feed that
ball out to that left-hand side whenever
they can
[Applause]
Side by Sully March finds Tarik lamty
and it's well covered by Gomez there's
the pace of lamp tea which is always
such a big part of his game
by soli March who's done well to get it
back into that team that's come off
Brighton corner kick
a big role isn't it for an 18 year old
that
big statement from Jurgen klopp
an area of the pitch that he really
feels needs freshening up I think and
that's just a key example young player
coming in in such an experienced role
so first point of the game is the
Brighton Corner fewer than three minutes
played
Sonny march with that delivery well
taken by Alison
[Applause]
and he's just failed as he tried to
deliver that
good take wasn't it
right over his head had to be strong
with the challenge coming in from
McAllister
goes forward
and cater has just got a around Lewis
Duncan he's found Mohamed Salah in front
of him Webster with the black Salah for
Liverpool off the line by Doug just
slashed by Nikita
cleared away off the goal line by
Lewiston
ritoma into McAllister already a really
good taste about this game Pascal grows
striving forward
but by kunate he just holds on to it too
long there Pascal gross
smacks his hands in frustration because
he knows the space he was there that
ball has to be left in behind if he does
that
Liverpool are in big trouble what a good
couple of counter attacks we've seen
already
[Applause]
Lewis dunk off the line there Steve
incredible clearance off the line from
Louis dunk
until very nearly
in front very early on in this time
like injured the course at the moment
for Liverpool and there's a canate in
possession of those Central defensive
births at the moment
[Applause]
scene from the Tomah as well on that
left-hand side I mean
he's so calm under pressure and
technically when he's dribbling and
running with the ball he's excellent
it's the uh
[Applause]
gross has played right back left back
and number 10 Central Midfield today
[Applause]
[Music]
a mistake by gross Tiago onto it quickly
well recovered Lewiston
[Applause]
Mohamed Salah got close doing everything
he can to quiet salad with options
[Applause]
you can see Santa cut inside and shoot
from that kind of position it just shows
you maybe where he's at the moment in
terms of belief and confidence probably
a little bit down in the the usual Mo
Salah that we see at this stage of the
season
[Music]
[Applause]
Alexander Arnold wonderful ball bent off
the outside of his Boot and Salah wins
the corner off estupina great vision
from Alexander on already in this
opening six minutes we've probably seen
more from Liverpool than we saw in the
whole 90 minutes in the Premier League
game two weeks ago
certainly got a bit more purpose and
Edge to them about about them
it's very Trent Alexander Arnold isn't
it
vision
and the ability to execute with that
right foot outside of the boot the pace
of the pass was superb and I should
imagine this delivery from the corner
won't be too bad either
Alexander Arnold
and so much hasn't quite dealt with it
then dunk
right underneath that
gross I saw it blocked nearly fell to
gapo has fallen to Harvey Elliott
foreign
[Applause]
dragging that onto his right foot always
cutting across the ball
from Harvey Elliott
[Applause]
this is where Brian likes to play a lot
now
they did an excellent
Premier League game just being able to
draw Liverpool in the confidence to play
out from the back in those tight areas
[Applause]
to throw it
so he matched Solly March in the foot
race
[Applause]
about why Liverpool
not at the level that they've become
accustomed to
some physical some psychological the
truth is it's probably a bit of
everything
a little bit of instability in the club
as well isn't there something for sale
changes things a little bit you know
it's like the key backroom Personnel
have left alternative Recruitment and at
this level slightly Take Your Eye Off
the ball really has a big impact and it
has done for Liverpool
[Applause]
from foreign
get a touch on it
[Applause]
could be a long afternoon out there on
the right hand side for Trent Alexander
Arnold it really could this guy
is in super confident form
[Applause]
kind of as Paul intended for Andrew
Robertson but well covered by Sonny
March
[Applause]
the fouled by Thiago free kick to
Brighton
lovely confident play again from
Brighton Pascal gross with the touch and
just use his body to Shield this ball
not allow
Thiago to win it just hacks him down in
the end but play it from that corner the
pass from Sully March two Pascal gross
was
really good
we count three fouls in that challenge
yeah he had a few hacks didn't he
[Applause]
played Neil Neil
but uh lots of Promise about this game
[Applause]
being bright and do look like they're
just sit in Ferguson
a little bit deeper that's a great ball
that
well dealt with by if I hit my konate
because with Tomah had made that good
run
[Applause]
Thiago there ahead of gross
for Liverpool
let's Liverpool were chasing trophies on
four fronts last season
people have had this uh theory that it's
been psychologically damaging for them
to go so close
four and end up in inverted commas only
with two
I think sometimes when you've been
at a club for that amount of time that
Jurgen klopp has style has a little bit
to play in terms of how much your
longevity is because Liverpool play a
real high Octane Game during that season
after season after season season can be
draining for a group of players in
comparison to a Manchester City
who would just control games have the
ball a lot of the time slow it down
difficult play on that front foot all
the time
I think the the style can weigh a little
bit heavy over the seasons back to back
which game Landmark has a manager over
the course of some 23 seasons
it's interesting that his previous Club
at a similar time they had a little bit
of a dip as well didn't they Dortmund
and Dortmund they did yeah
well he's picked up the reins where
Graham Potter left off and if anything
he's improved
[Applause]
for nothing
yeah
for Robinson
[Applause]
which they're defending in this first
half
[Applause]
possession but not much penetration at
the moment from Liverpool
attention this is the box right here
bright enough sat in really well very
organized out of possession
not allowing Liverpool to play through
the middle of the pitch
foreign
[Applause]
in the right place to deny Ferguson
well we've seen goal line clearances at
both ends now that should be a goal
Brighton patient defensive work win the
ball the spacers Robertson's gone in
advance he's on the left-hand side of
Liverpool's defense since Sully March
picks out a brilliant cross I have to
say really gets his head up and that
should be one nil
Alexander Arnold in a great position In
fairness to him but Ferguson should just
smash that past him even go high into
the roof of the net
not sure how it's still nil nil after a
uh really engrossing first quarter now
but it is
so much here
watch with the drive he's finished
this season Solly March which is not
something you've ever been able to say
about him in the past that's always been
the thing that's lacking with Solly
March brilliant player doesn't score
enough goals from the positions he gets
himself in but he's put that right
recently
is that tackle from bicessage
on Pascal gross the referee allows play
on for the shot
it's just had a word where the young
would feel it yeah it's a little bit
late wasn't it
it's definitely
does the ground doesn't win the ball
it's late on Gross it's not the most
aggressive or dangerous of tackles I've
ever seen I can understand that
perspective from Jurgen klopp but
missed the ball and you go to ground and
you commit as every chance you're going
to come out with a yellow card and
it'll be a lot more tackles he's going
to have to make in this game by tessich
be careful
family is Dad
played for Red Star Belgrade and Celta
Vigo hence Vigo being the place of his
birth
[Applause]
football for Brighton Jason Steele 32
year old it's only his 14th game to the
club since joining from Sunderland
playing second fiddle to Robert Sanchez
in the mate
Challenge from Robertson for referee
David Couture free King
dived in it from Ferguson
decision very experienced linesman
not enough contact there he knows what
he wants there Ferguson
he's got the wrong side of Robertson but
he's nowhere near enough contact to go
down
[Applause]
those Liverpool Players whose contracts
will
be up at the end of the season and who
it seems is unlikely to be around next
campaign that's an awkward fault yeah
there's a little bit of trouble here
Kate up
your head on the floor
really can have some kind of impact he's
up and on his feet hopefully okay
[Applause]
foreign
[Music]
and Liverpool is in this competition 115
years ago
one more draw in Sussex Liverpool won
the replay
and of encouragement for Liverpool from
the touch line to get after the ball
frightening doing it well Liverpool just
can't keep possession across the back
line into Midfield they're giving it
away a lot with the pressure that
Brighton are putting forward
yesterday
and they're ahead of Navi keita and Kato
has fouled and coma
[Applause]
was played through mitoma to win the
ball here gets his body in in the line
you can see clearly contacts matoma and
then a little bit of the ball but
it's a bit clumsy from keita
for Liverpool
party
[Music]
time
Ferguson metoma it's got a diploma in
dribbling that kid Anderson with the
same didn't quite hit it as clearly as
you would have liked
but amazing passenger play really the
Fate here just to send everyone and come
inside absolutely brilliant lovely flip
from Ferguson another little Dummy from
mitoma I mean he's so clever
how he sees it and reacts that little
shimmy there just completely commits Joe
Gomez
slightly off balance with the left
footage strike just
scuffs it into the ground but lovely
play again from matoma
to Mohamed Salah
[Applause]
if she says play on canate's Challenge
on Ferguson
Andrew Robertson
the right foot was just out a tad bit
unusual
for Alexander Arnold he's normally
absolutely inch perfect with that right
foot
that's going to need to be today
activity is a massive Park
of how Liverpool are and how dangerous
they are as a team from scoring
is at least once or twice in a game he
puts a ball in which is
a brilliant assist it does it so often
but it's almost in the teams need to
bring that offensive play because the
sacrifice the defensive side of his game
and you know you're not going to get
that from Alexander Arnold at the moment
[Applause]
foreign
looking for Welbeck canate's favorite
here on this ground
[Applause]
that's good play from canate
didn't have to do too much just had to
get his body across and block that run
of Welbeck
foreign
[Applause]
the kind of opportunity he just feeds
off well he's Central position which is
brilliant times the Run looks offside
but I think lamptey is playing him on
slightly deeper
you're absolutely right Steve from that
position
how many times have you seen Mo Salah
just bury this into the back of the net
and he really doesn't get a good contact
on the ball at all
much better position much better
foresight from Liverpool to be creative
and be direct and play those forward
passes but
Shane we didn't have the quality finish
at the end
it's about that chance I'm sure that uh
one side
[Applause]
interesting game
yeah very
tactical battle and
quite cagey both teams trying to play
out and some really good pressing going
on
possession statistics are exactly shared
Brighton don't have 60 plus possession
in a game
particularly here
[Applause]
good for Webster to get some minutes
the periphery over the last couple of
months
[Music]
who's just come into that role and been
excellent for them at center-back
I think that Brighton have made this
season
Chelsea
Chelsea yeah of course
Homer
you say brightness
marginally the more dangerous of the two
sides and yet actually in terms of
chances as you could say Sal is
obviously a big one and then the Duncan
one after that
pretty even but I feel you the the
writing just a little bit more dangerous
going forward Liverpool look a little
bit more susceptible to conceive than
Brighton
October
it's a great ball by Elliot into Salah
[Applause]
darling you just enjoyed it
here's Cody Gap Folk
Elliot and Salah are with Him Gatto
carrying it looking for Salah it's come
back to Salah good reactions by Steele
nothing highly convinced Salah is on
side but with goalkeeping I think
there's an early chance to play it here
now put that ball in behind for Salah
he hops to go with it jackpot but he is
on side when the ball's played it's a
good interception from lamptey
it's more the position that you're used
to see in gatpo isn't it dropping deeper
picking the ball up and then driving
with it
of their three group matches
[Applause]
well back
Sunday March 19 on the overlap almost
bought March
sight of goal that ran from lamptey but
it's well blocked
this is the importance of that run even
if you don't get the ball as a fullback
what it does for the man on the ball is
create that space for them to go inside
and get shots off exactly like that that
Solly March just took
[Applause]
it
we had the ball punched out of his hands
by Harvey Elliot a moment ago
feigning to throw it back to Gatto and
then
dropping it
[Applause]
estupina
it's a good ball
Joe Gomez healed in it
it's gonna be a goal kick
well everything he touches at the moment
mitoma is of top quality
One Touch pass this time not a dribble
perfectly weighted
just can't quite take it any stridest
opinion but they've got a nice little
link up going on that left-hand side
haven't they
best opinion and matoma
really good attacking threat
Kate up finding Mohamed Salah
Elliot driving forward gap for driving
forward it's Harvey Elliot for Liverpool
and
[Applause]
the man is goal of molyneux fired
Liverpool into the fourth round of the
FA Cup has put them in front at Brighton
Harvey Elliott still just a teenager
Lewis done takes a real gamble here just
to get in front of Salah and okay he
wins the ball but the ball then pops
straight out to Salah and bright and
they're in trouble they're outnumbered
the Run looks on side to me from Harvey
Elliott and I have to say with his left
foot but being a left-footed player the
finish with the right foot is absolutely
excellent just gets his it has a little
glance very early knows exactly where
Steel's coming out and just guides that
into the far post
don't there's anything wrong with the
execution but VAR are checking
this right at the beginning of the move
possibly Danny Welbeck was appealing for
something it might have been a handball
there it is
[Applause]
Nicole stands
that would have been harsh wouldn't it
I think when it's 70 yards away yeah it
would have been
Liverpool League been threatening
haven't they
both teams threatening but Liverpool a
couple of times times on the counter
[Applause]
example of just a little bit of over
committing from Louis stunk I tried to
win that ball
just left him short at the back and
Liverpool take full advantage it's very
much momentarily was behind Gomez
[Applause]
all right
that's Homer looking to reply for
Brighton I think it's got enough of the
ball there
well it's Harvey Elliott's fifth goal
for Liverpool
all the previous four matches in which
he scored
them by nine goals to kneel against
Bournemouth and won by seven goals to
one against Rangers
sure they'll get that scoreline today
[Applause]
held back for Brighton
marginally against
sentences McAllister for Brighton
to March
decided to punch
it was a decent Cross of his left foot
there as well from Tariq lamptey
[Applause]
how about my cat car thinking he's
hoping he'd get a free kick
[Applause]
has just gone out of play from midterm
who cost Brighton
somewhere in the region of two and a
half million pounds it's an
extraordinary deal
see that's where uh Brighton were
appealing for handball
that came off his thigh onto his hand
very little contact with the arm
good finish
really good finish actually not easy
that hasn't got a lot to aim at Harvey
Elliott
see why Brighton are repealing the
handball it clearly was
you know a handball from catering Center
the ball with jam between his leg and
his arm
[Applause]
at the moment you have to it has to lead
almost immediately correct it's too far
it was away from the actual goal going
in which is why it's been allowed to
to move forward but Liverpool only
looked really threatening from those
scenarios it's going to be a turnover in
Midfield it's going to be a
the wrong decision from a Brighton
player that leads to Liverpool having a
chance at the moment as opposed to
Liverpool really building the play up
from the back so bright they've got them
penned in nicely
[Applause]
young Irishman Republic of Ireland
player and um
I can only imagine it will be a very
short space of time before he gets
international honors because Ireland
aren't blessed with uh haven't been for
a number of years with reliable goal
scorers really since
Robbie Keane I suppose but um this guy
looks cut out for it
could be a blessing for them couldn't
they for sure
otherwise always on the moose look great
anticipation
even when Liverpool have the ball he's
kind of anticipating if his teammates
win it where's he going to drop and he's
on the move there already before by
catas have almost gone on to that
all right
towards his own goal with sort of was
there
[Music]
this gives us a quick comparison
but if you will between the first 36
minutes of this game and the league game
first 36 minutes of The League game you
watched two weeks ago there's not much
comparison to be honest in terms of the
Liverpool that have turned up here today
are completely different
look more organized more at it certainly
a much bigger goal threat in what
they've created so far in the opening 36
minutes and Brighton though are pretty
similar I have to say
consistently playing well
[Applause]
Salah we should have scored before
Elliot did
touch that
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
on the ball
just indicating that to me Sims wanting
to head it out for a throw in but the
moment he headed it it just
kicked right and out for a corner
into one Corners in Brighton's favor one
to nil goals in Liverpool's
[Applause]
foreign
Ty for Brighton
big big deflection on its way
Liverpool's goalkeeper was flying in the
wrong direction as the ball moved in the
other
all square
maybe that Lewiston got the final touch
on this
I think it was done
who the ball here as lamptey has too
much space on the edge of the box it
gets clear but there's nobody in that
area too much time for lamptey to arrive
on this ball and I think it just hits
Louis stunt whether or not he flicks out
a little foot here
this is a good angle to see it I'm sure
he'll be claiming it somehow just there
oh yeah he did just try and guide that
into the net it's a clever little touch
from Lewis dunk
a really subtle piece of play or whether
or not it hits his standing foot either
way just tries to pull his body out of
the way
and it hits him perfectly wrong foot to
Allison absolutely no chance to react
well it's Lewis dunks goal all right
it's 1-1
I think that little smile just says it
all Steve don't you
just first goal of the season
approaching 400 games for Lewis donkeys
like the uh
thread through the old stick of Brighton
Rock it doesn't seem to matter what's
around him or
Shake bright and play Lewis dunk is
always right at the heart of whatever
they do
but they're under pressure again here
as Elliott tries to force it Forward
Webster's cushion header to steal
I mean you have to say Brian have
probably deserved to be level in this
game going in at half time
[Applause]
I think he'll mind how it goes in
that's one of those players actually has
a uh
an outstanding uh Runners scoring own
goals against his name over the years
Lewis he scored six own goals in his
career at Brighton
truly won against Liverpool
scored 200 goals in the same game
against Liverpool a few years ago
that is a bad day at the office it's the
nature in how he defends he throws
everything at it blocks tackles
you're always going to get a few that
deflecting the wrong way it was a young
play when I was at the club
it's a really bright talent I think Gus
Point really was quite harsh on him
trying to knock him into shape and get
him into the right mentality to play and
it's really matured well and like you
say it's been absolutely ever present
across the seasons for Brighton
and it doesn't really matter if they
play a four or a three no never
formation they play one of them is
always Louis stuff yeah absolutely it's
comfortable in either
maybe better in a three if I'm honest
because I think it just allows him to to
come out with boys got a lovely Ranger
long range of passing
Ellie Elliot all poor touch
and lamji's clearance nearly hit Mohamed
Salah
referee wants treatment here for Harvey
Elliott it was a great chat for him to
get his second of the game
well he's just picked up great positions
in this game Javier look at the way he
just makes that little run behind pulls
off the moment gatpo's there
and that lovely role that he's playing a
bit deeper and how about that for a
challenge
that is commitment from Tariq lamp to
expression on his face says it all I'm
going to win that ball
does nearly just deflect into the middle
of the pitch and it could have backfired
but
brilliant tackle from lamptey it's a
slightly heavy touch from Elliot yeah
yeah it wasn't perfect just gave him a
nibble
boy did he take it
not ahead from Harvey Elliot suggests
he's okay
the youngest player ever to start a game
for Liverpool and previously the
youngest player ever to represent Fulham
he's still only 19 he's got a bash off
the backside of Jason Steele the
goalkeeper
let's look good in that advanced role
isn't he
took up doesn't mind going Central I
think he's happy to just drift into that
Central area and if gakpo's gonna be as
deep as what he has been a couple of
times
Taylor Made for him just to make that
little running behind
me where his Liverpool future lies
however because you must remember that
they also have on the injured list at
the moment the likes of Diego jota and
Luis Diaz Darwin Nunez is on the bench
here the Salah there's firmino so uh
a little bit competition three for
Liverpool are going to be hard to get
foreign
[Applause]
tie so far
what's up
oh
[Music]
sufficient
assignment address indicated there'll be
a minimum of two pack of minutes yes
well back and Ferguson are in the middle
acting
cross which Ferguson pushes down
stair trying to hit Mohamed Salah for
coming back and helping out
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
oh my God
taking advantage of the coming together
McAllister
you're not in Liverpool play through
Brighton from this area the pitch match
at all in this game
about plenty of possession in around the
back there which will
bump the stats up
in terms of breaking lines and cutting
through the Midfield and progressing
forwards they haven't really been able
to do that too much in this opening 45.
which is nearly at an end
there is David Cook's whistle so an
excellent first 45 minutes it really has
been Harvey Elliott with a very tidy
finish to put Liverpool in front but
Lewis stuck with a flick on a shot from
Tariq lamptey which diverted the ball
away from Liverpool's goalkeeper Alison
with the equalizer for Brighton more
much more entertainment to come in the
second half good tie this half time at
the AmEx brand new noval been one
Liverpool One
Adam Webb's development often plays
right back for Brighton but he'll be
playing as the right-sided center half
as they kick off the second period with
uh
Joel feltman now alongside Louis dunk
there's another player who's relatively
versatile isn't he
Joel veltman lots of experience
I agree I think it must be a problem
with Adam Webster had a decent first 45
minutes and
I think that change would have happened
unless there's some kind of injury issue
of some kind
here goes lamptey
confronted by Robertson looking for the
return got by Joe Gomez
[Applause]
player who featured in that dramatic
Champions League two-legged semi-final
against Tottenham Hotspur back in uh
2019 wasn't it you know four years ago
now
an unbelievable Game Wouldn't it yeah
one one he'll probably be trying to
forget
okay
[Applause]
Robertson was tempted into another shirt
from unwell back there momentarily
no changes at half time as they were in
the first period he goes uh
just on the right side of legal from the
Liverpool fullback well just about but
he's under Arnold nowhere near the ball
here just tries to run across his path
and
yeah tries to commit the foul but the
distances he has between him and matoma
when matoma builds up ahead of speed and
he's running out here you just feel he's
going to Glide past him every time
foreign
just to chest this one down to Thiago
but the ball just drops a little bit
lower and that right arm comes across
from Gap vote
so much with across dangerous
good ball in that was
so inviting this from Solly March
I think matoma really gambles just quite
early enough to get across the face of
Alexander Arnold
once the ball bounced it was always
going to be too high for him
off well Brighton
had any possession yet since
steel to feltman Great touch
[Applause]
just caught by Cody but his first
touching fighting gapro to try and Win
It
he has good pressure from Liverpool they
sensed danger and tried to push in on
Brighton and see their gakpo a little
bit late on veltman just catches his
ankle
but they don't mind taking a bit of a
risk right in that area of the pitch
they're not just gonna
clear their lines or kick it long they
they'll play out from any situation
by dunk to well back
[Applause]
will be in the book soon it was clever
little touch here from McAllister sees
the
the Run coming from gatpo and just
drives across his path knows exactly
what he's doing takes the contact
and two
Mr might if he feels he's uh we're
coming from that challenge
see this free kick I seem to remember he
scored brilliant free kick against
Leicester earlier this season from this
kind of position
S as well actually my only concern is
he's got up from that challenge and he's
carrying his right leg a little bit
whether or not he feels ready to
take on a strike of this magnitude I'm
not too sure he's walking away from the
ball now and leaving it up to this man
who's dunk
oh
foreign
[Applause]
gets plenty of movement on the ball
his technique he tries to hit that one
over look at the dip and swerve on that
great angle here really did drop down
quickly had Alison scampering a little
bit
[Applause]
just as fantasies at the end of training
every day by uh stepping up for three
kicks on the edge of the penalty area oh
he's certainly that type of player when
he's done
[Music]
bright
[Applause]
I say that we know it's uh
sought after Alexis McAllister would be
too they've got an awful lot of players
that other clubs would covet
this season
I kind of add the Sumer to that list of
type of players as well can't you not
too long before then
that's in the summer window yeah yeah
it's a lot of talent isn't it leaving
the squad a lot of money about 150
million pounds worth has come in
[Applause]
put your hand in the transfer market
because uh
presumably have no need of
another injection of cash so they can
hold those who want their players to a
certain amount of Hostage
what's incredible they seem to appear to
have kind of layers of that Talent
filtering through all the time you know
consumer goes McAllister steps in
cookery goes estopina steps in and
doesn't seem to weaken the team too much
[Applause]
even when the manager left it didn't
seem to weaken 19 like say even made
potentially made him stronger
foreign
[Applause]
Potter does have to
take a lot of credit for a lot of the
work he did building this group of
players and the way that they play
[Applause]
Steel
I was frustrated look straight away
should not be caught offside you're the
furthest man you've got time to stay on
it's a poor position from matoma
in what would have been a really
interesting situation again
Christian header Thiago is there
[Applause]
it's that touch there from Ferguson
again
cushion One Touch
you look at the wave played you think
he's going to be a bit physical and
bullish but he's got that quality of
touch as well
showing that error
[Applause]
away from Alexander Arnold Alison with
the half block brought down by March and
over the top from Pascal gross
but it all starts with matoma well he's
just got the beating of Trent Alexander
Arnold at the moment two players there
it's just far too easy for him to drop
his shoulder and go around the outside
too sure if salah's really doing too
much to help Alexander Arnold though in
terms of communication and where they
want to show him
as the strike from
gross in the middle of the park but
Oma on the left-hand side Brian will
just be filtering that ball out as early
as possible get it out there early as
much space around Trent Alexander Aranda
as they can and just leaving 1v1
[Applause]
foreign
cater this is almost Liverpool's first
attack of the second half
Alexander Arnold to Harvey Elliott
has fallen and well sure the Gap toe
didn't get in salah's way there
there's the cross that we always see
from Trent Alexander Arnold
I know there's going to be one or two
moments in this game where he delivers
winning quality which that was
I think you're spot on they get in each
other's ways nobody
really commits to that it's poor from
Liverpool's perspective because that's
such an inviting cross and for me gapos
got the momentum there to take control
of that go and hit it
should have been more dominant
might have been offside anyway
s off to me
Milner Nunez and Oxley Chamberlain all
getting ready for Liverpool
it's Joe Anderson
look like they need an injection of
something of a pool don't they start in
the second half
got in the game at all yet by that cross
from
Alexander Arnold
[Applause]
very interesting to see who's coming off
to James Miller
Alexander
so
yeah
he's now 37 years of age
relish going up against Natoma if that
is the change that the open top is
considering
is the triple change now head for
Liverpool and it is Trent Alexander
Arnold coming off at James Miller at 37
will come on to deal with retirement
under Arnold has found difficult
to accept but I think Jurgen klopp seen
enough of that 1v1 Jewel to know
it's going to hurt Liverpool very very
soon if he doesn't do something about it
and he seems James Milner is the answer
to that problem
Henderson
for Harvey Elliott
sighting and important to get his Pace
into the game for Liverpool been lacking
that reel
physical presence and ability to run
Beyond them past people he certainly
brings that Nunez
killing yourself pretty well for Liberty
so far in the early days of his career
in anfield it's a big fee and some
people have
sort of question whether he's really
looked an 80 million pound player at
times
you know they may have a case in some
respect but in his first season in a new
league
I remember he's uh
only uh reasonably recently moved to a
new continent he does already have 10
goals for Liverpool yeah it's not bad
it's not bad and I think that the uh the
spotlight has been on him so heavily
because they haven't had other players
available to lighten that goal scoring
load Mo Sal has been a little bit off it
in terms of contributions with assists
and goals
Salah the angle's horrible for him but
he does have support still got a touch
on it and it didn't fall for Gap though
[Applause]
Mountain
there's Trent alexander-esque wasn't it
from James Milner brought on to do a
defensive job but straight up the other
end and puts in a ball like that
they're going to ground two years later
with the clearance Pascal gross to Joel
feltman
[Applause]
there's the pass look at that inch
perfect Lewis dunk at full stretch can't
do anything about it and it's a good
goalkeeper from steel that because he
commits there he comes all the way out
of the goal
kind of gambles that he has to intercept
that cross and gets a solid hand on it
[Applause]
we've cut very good it's just poised
perfectly isn't it after an hour
one one with both teams looking
threatening
tough one to call
[Applause]
15 attempts in the game it's been uh
okay which is Promised goals and
delivered so far two of them
[Applause]
say second Liverpool player in David
coote's book
quality confident play from Brighton
and this is Ferguson again always on the
move as a center-back it's very
difficult to win that ball and the
center forwards always got movement and
running across you and from behind you
and kanate
just couldn't get there first and gets
his Yellow Card
Gomez
it's good so if you get phone now Lewis
tank is chasing him and has pulled him
back that'll be a yellow card for the
Brighton Skipper all day long
Lewis dunk just does
what he wants McAllister to do early on
in this move he had a chance McAllister
just to foul him
early on and instead Louis dunk has to
do quite a blatant shirt Paul
it's very close to his own box as well
good run from Gap vote
[Applause]
free kick Lewis done now
he's organizing the defensive wall in
Tandem and his goalkeeper there's uh
two in it
from the edge of the penalty area
there might have been a bit of shirt
pulling there Liverpool certainly
thought as much
[Applause]
seated a file just have a look at this
on konate
a lot of bodies in that area
too sure if there's actually a
[Applause]
it's in go to ground perhaps as to
pinyan from behind it's just got a
little bit too much of him but referee
felt canate went down easily
Gilmore is getting ready for Brighton
yesterday
[Music]
[Applause]
isn't it
confident
[Applause]
okay this is Darwin Nunez for Liverpool
Henderson Thiago
another one two with Robertson still
scrapping for it Liverpool that nearly
came off
lovely idea from Thiago pass and follow
this area of the pitch good spot for
Nunez but just a little bump
into Robertson in the Box tries to get
the the
pass back and Brighton
really get the bodies in there able to
deal with it
[Applause]
foreign
World Cup winner on the pitch
World Cup winners medal from his dad who
Brazilian team of 1994
is an italian-born Spanish International
with Brazilian Heritage playing in
England here goes Mohamed Salah
foreign
[Applause]
straight away James Milner has tried to
make a statement on matoma
tight a couple of times made that tackle
just to let him know it's not going to
get it easy against him
so
it's Danny Welbeck who makes way
and
comes on the 21 year old
Scott
is on for what is only a ninth
appearance for Brighton he joined the
club
from Chelsea just before Graham Potter
moved the other way
Brighton just switching to that four two
three one a little bit more with
McAllister it looks like gonna play that
slightly more advanced Midfield role
number 10 with Gilmore and gross as the
two sitting in front of the two
center-backs
pretty much the normal shape that
Brighton would play I can't remember the
last time I've seen him play with two up
as they had for the first 66 minutes of
this game I think if you
could Welbeck and Ferguson it almost
kind of just guides you to that
formation doesn't it
it's been pretty effective has to be
said they've played well Brighton
are one by uh cat cope
the free kick to Liverpool
we are now Midway through the second
half of this game remember we
do have replays in the Forefront of the
FA Cup so it could be that for the
second round in succession Liverpool
need two bites at the Cherry in an FA
Cup tie having beaten wolves in round
three
antenna
milna
capto Milner
took behind by Louis Duncan Liverpool
are saying that they felt nil they've
just got a little arm because he was
about to deliver that cross yeah it's
good honest play from James milder stays
on his feet and stays strong for that
cross
opinion
certainly wasn't too close to the ball
as he bounced his shoulder into him I
think that's what Liverpool and James
Milner weren't too happy with
[Applause]
Milner's delivery for Liverpool
over the top of Charlotte for a tree
that's a shy
foreign
[Applause]
James Milner has been he won his first
with two FA Cup winners medals
[Applause]
example
so
Fitness wise how he looks looks after
his body to be playing at this level of
that age is a real achievement
little fans enjoying Darwin Nunes
killing trash on the man in possession
it is a goal kick to fight
[Applause]
the pressure isn't it look how high
Liverpool have started their Tiago all
the way in Henderson all the way in
trying to apply pressure to Brighton
because they're just playing out no
matter what Brighton doesn't feel like
they're going to go long today and just
try and bypass that area of the pitch
and hit the front
they're going through or wide every time
it's interesting isn't it the Darwin
Nunez is on the left of the three and
gapo is is down the middle
certainly where Jurgen props easy and
I'll actually bring a player to the club
and spend that kind of money and playing
in a position where you don't really
think he's going to play for you
straight away
you know we've all been assuming that
he's playing there because Nunez isn't
available or firmino can't play there or
whatever but perhaps that really is the
role that Jurgen klopp sees him for
filling foot for Liverpool
[Applause]
into the last 20 minutes of the AmEx
well controlled by estrupina
[Applause]
curling Ball by Duncan to metoma canate
coming across great ball in off well
Alison gets a big pat on the back from
Andrew Robertson it was brilliantly
played from with Tommy to March well
March cannot believe it this is
brilliant from the Tomah look at the
pass outside the right boot and it just
hits Alison
bounces back off and hits Solly March
straight in the face I mean or in the
chest it's a sure goal
just lifts it a couple of inches more
it's in the back of the net brilliant
play from Brighton now matoma again
stupina
Joe Gomez Sonny March not by Robertson
headed out by Milner
gross
canate for Liverpool who are hanging on
here Henderson
Mohamed Salah
[Applause]
Nunez into Mohamed Salah who's fouled by
Tariq Mountain
well tough for Tariq lamptey here
perhaps he doesn't get any of the ball
but he's not masses of contact on salary
that
I think salah's momentum makes it look a
lot worse as he's falling backwards
anyway
not too much contact but certainly
doesn't win the ball lap team
[Applause]
giving away my gross to Robertson
shot there and then jump to pass to
nowhere in particular I thought the shot
was coming
I think that was the better option as
well have a go from that area
[Music]
shouting at Thiago something or I'll
take him off
I'm not sure if he was referring to
Nunez there in terms of just he looked
like he was a bit annoyed that he didn't
have the shot Maybe
that's what he's on the pitch for be a
threat you get half a yard pull the
trigger
dominated
possession in this second half
relax inside to score a goal
s
by Tariq lamptey
Thiago almost picked out Darwin Nunez
felt in the set and how early did Joel
velt will drop into that space and read
that
used all of his experience Joel veltman
made it look easy it was great
anticipation
[Applause]
it comes on the head of uh right
goalkeeper didn't he Jason Steele
I'm hunting a couple of challenges and
now running at Gomez
to Henderson
recovers
it's a full run actually as Muhammad
Salah
slows it down and finds Stefan which you
teach this is
Robertson
[Applause]
and he's had limited opportunity
Robertson to get forward in this game
maybe that's something that he's had to
slightly reduce for Liverpool at the
moment is more of focus and attention on
being good defensively
giving them a solid base to build from
than him getting forward I think he
sacrificed that a little bit Andy
Robertson
[Applause]
[Music]
it's kunatic
[Applause]
Ally
without
thank you
is on here
he asked them to win that race with
Sully March good starting position as
they say for goalkeepers we had to get
there
slowly March running from all the way
across the other side of the pitch
together
the pool has broken the fourth
official's board with a very inopportune
moment because Liverpool
would quite like to get Curtis Jones off
to revert to Old School Technology
surprised they haven't got a backup
[Applause]
against
anything about
[Applause]
Gilmore and he's just gone into a little
bit of a lull like the uh the Calm
before the storm as
much for a winner in the latter stages
of the game
both teams really fighting hard for
possession of the ball
lots of quick Pace turnovers and
little loose balls being won and then
overturned again and team's trying to
play out it's been a fascinating game
here is Curtis Jones
to come on for Liverpool by far his most
memorable moment in the Liverpool Jersey
came in this competition you may
remember it when uh
you have been cop picked a very very
youthful Liverpool side for an FA Cup
tie against neighbors Everton at anfield
and
that man curled in the winning goal and
a brilliant goal it was he's on for
Thiago
oh
foreign
wanted to take it without bouncing but
realized he couldn't get there then had
to adjust his position done well to
deal with that ball in the end
[Music]
[Applause]
tonight's Gilmore into McAllister
estupina
giving away carelessly by Gilmore Jones
Nunez
they do lose it and it's sunny March
[Applause]
just kept that in it's not a good
clearance by Gomez
and Ferguson from close range couldn't
steer a goalwoods
what an important block that is from
canate
Sully march here he sees by cesic and he
just knows he's got the beating of him
on the outside
Perfect Touch cuts it back and look at
that for a block
brilliant
[Applause]
certainly Roberto deserve his 17th game
as Brighton manager and three of them
have been against Liverpool
three will draw at anfield a three-nil
win here both in the league
and this on a knife edge 10 minutes to
go
there Alison's
delivery
[Applause]
only delivery which is out a little bit
McAllister went to Brown
the fans are hooting and hollering but
play goes on he's had a few of them in
this game hasn't he canate just about
close enough in contact with the ball to
Warrant that kind of shoulder charge
great early spot for envelopement though
wasn't it to play that over the top and
down the line
looks like a foul to me yeah it's the
position that he puts his shoulder in
you'd have to say that McAllister
probably is the wrong side of him so the
contact then is more from behind
gets away with it canate
mood to get up at the moment Alexis
McAllister
[Applause]
let's have another look
close it's almost on the side Steve it's
very very tight to say whether that is a
a foul from behind because they're both
close enough to the ball to Warrant
going for it or whether or not he's on
the side of McAllister and it's really
on that fine line and then if you judge
it to be a foul you have to start
thinking about is it denial of a goal
scorer scoring opportunity absolutely
[Applause]
well Alexis McAllister is getting some
treatment here
it's called twice in
Brighton's third round victory at the
Riverside Stadium
against Middlesbrough did McAllister
must be that contact
on the back of the neck of canate's arm
on McAllister what he has the problem
with
I can't see too much other than that as
to why he'd still be down
[Applause]
tap
I think with seven minutes to go the way
the game has been particularly in the
second half Matt would you agree that it
might be Liverpool we'd be happy to go
to a replay in Brighton I I agree with
that I think Brighton have have edged it
in terms of dominating the play being
more creative looking more solid as a
team
Liverpool have relied on on those
counters really or just the turnover of
possession and hitting Brighton when
they're a little bit
too far exposed so
Liverpool Liverpool be happy to take
this back for a replay
and McAllister is okay and as you just
saw
Liverpool's uh Brazilian fabinho
is coming on Stefan my chich makes way
it is education completed
six to play one month
very likely be enough to take whoever
scores it into the fifth round of the FA
Cup
[Applause]
should be here
so it's not the graph of the top five
Brighton players by the way with
accurate passing in the opposition half
it's the top five players in the game it
just all happened to be Brighton Place
that says a lot doesn't it just asking
who do we feel has edged it and will
Liverpool be happy to take this to a
replay I think they will
that just backs that up
to try to get so much back into the feet
of the
uh
who has made a less than illustrious
start to his uh brief appearance on the
pitch here I think that's two touches he
gave the ball away with the first and
he's got a yellow card for a second he
knows it as well
really trying to hide the fact that
it was a poor challenge poorly timed it
can happen when you've been on the bench
for a while
coming on trying to get used to the
speed of the game and it's a fast pace
in this closing minutes
there's two poor tackles that's a bad
one
I'm trying an ankle a Ferguson really
catches him
yes next Liverpool appearance will be
his two hundreds it's been a good
signing from Monaco but he's not had a
great season
until they're happy with that either
does he looks very disappointed in
himself yeah he's gotta gotta get over
that sometimes when your confidence is a
bit low and you
you're not feeling like you're up to the
speed of the game
look any better with repetition does it
no
we're near the ball
he's feeling bad on the actual choice
that he made to actually go for that
it's
one of those ones where you endanger the
safety of the opposition in a in a
reckless fashion I think that comes
under that bracket
it's a really painful one
I'm going to make it changing Dennis
under the German Center forward is going
to be coming on has been uh
used pretty sparingly so far this season
by Brighton a player that was the top
scorer in the Belgian League last season
with Union San juas which are a
part of the club of Brighton
you can head from Lewis tuck to Jordan
Henderson here
he's a bit more upset with himself for
injuring him like that I think he knows
that it was a poor
decision to go for that ball and
Ferguson
doesn't look like he's going to continue
should be a devastating blow for a
young man who's made such an impressive
start
career in football yes
and his feet I'm very pleased to say
yeah it's good to see him walk off
[Applause]
[Music]
it's replaced
Dennis
[Music]
11th time this season he's come off the
bench to represent Brighton he has two
goals so far in his career with the club
he's a German 26 years old
and he's going to get 90 seconds Plus at
the time of this fourth round time
play of Steel
[Applause]
actually here is uh
as he makes his way around the pitch
straight into the medical room I should
think Gilmore
School
of course
[Applause]
a strong challenge it's a free kick to
Brighton
in fact it's really famous FA Cup
victories came out anfield against
Liverpool
40 years ago now they beat Liverpool in
a fourth round tie at anfield Jimmy case
who was a former Liverpool hero scored
Brighton's winning goal on that occasion
and it looks very much now as so they
will meet there again in a fourth round
replay
four decades on
but maybe not lanti forward mitoma
popping up right side looking for
lamptey Robertson stretching was always
going to be late it's always going to be
a yellow card
[Applause]
still there
Really Brave into the tackle he sees it
pop loose Roberts has fully committed
and he kind of jumps in as well
McAllister almost anticipating this
tackle going to come in but Robertson
certainly is the later one of the two
catches him right on top of the ankle
four yellow cards now in the game for
Liverpool
fabinho Robertson
[Applause]
moving terribly smoothly and normally as
Fergus as he's finally made his way
around the pitch
[Applause]
all right
son says can we play you every week
Roberto deserve it this feeling like he
does play Liverpool almost every week
just goes to a replay there'll be four
meetings
first
19 matches as Brighton boss that's
called gross for the free kick
stopina lobbed up nicely it's come to
Natoma brilliant feet what a finish from
caribitoma to send Brighton into the
fifth round of the FA Cup
absolutely brilliant from the Japanese
what a find he is
that is so calm so composed
and surely knocks the holders out of the
FA Cup
right into
Liverpool One
well if there was going to be a goal
worthy of winning this cup tie then this
is it what a finish from mitoma I love
this ball from Esther pinion just really
lops that to the back post but then it's
all about
matoma's poise
his quality his intelligence here how he
delays his touch has that there that
little drop inside and then the quick
finish with the right foot into the roof
of the net
I mean he's been the man of the match
for me before this goal
but this must just confirm it well they
are checking for a possible offside that
is one of the best finishes you are ever
likely to see talk about composure in a
tight area but is it going to count Neil
swarbrick is the video assistant referee
and they are double checking I mean it
must be on that initial delivery of the
free kick I assume
whether or not there was a Brighton
player straying offside possessed
opinion lobs that backwards from a
position
it looks like the line say it's gonna
count
Brighton
are heading into the fifth round of this
FA Cup surely
and what a joy that a goal of such
quality is not chalked off from a player
and such audacious skill
I mean that touch there sells Joe Gomez
and to hit it as quickly as what he does
when the other Liverpool players are
coming in for pressure
I mean it's just one step ahead in terms
of his thinking his reaction time he's
had a great afternoon
he's Darwin Nunez for a Liverpool though
at the other end
[Applause]
I think that was Mito who played it on
to Darwin Nunez wasn't it
[Applause]
foreign cup
it's being lofted high by Brighton
supporters five minutes were indicated
as you can see we're into the last of
them scored in that five minutes
to be a little bit more to add on right
now also considering bringing on the
actual van heck the Dutch Defender to
try and use up some time Milner to Jones
a free kick to Liverpool
[Applause]
brilliant brilliant goal
is slipping out of the open clock's
fingers
and goes the free kick
Henderson
foreign
[Applause]
Ty off the pitch
urgently he knows there's barely any
time left for Liverpool to restart
[Applause]
Liverpool's throw in
Joe Gomez with the throw Curtis Jones
[Applause]
I strongly suspect that when Jason
Steele takes his goal kick the referee
David Cook will blow his whistle and
Liverpool's time as FA cup holders
for their opportunity to defend the
trophy will be over
[Applause]
balance of the game
you can't deny that Brighton have
probably deserved this win
they've been Superior especially in this
second half
[Applause]
and there it is
Brighton have beaten Liverpool for the
second time in 15 days much tighter on
this occasion but it is Roberto deserve
beside who deservedly go into the fifth
round of the cup with a quite brilliant
winning goal from Karu mitoma
brilliantly brilliantly taken by the
Japanese
who is having a wonderful season and
Brighton Advance the holders are out it
has finished at the AmEx Brighton two
Liverpool One
[Applause]